A Guide to the Efim London papers FA978
Rockefeller Archive Center
Efim London papers
1903-1929
Rockefeller Archive Center
London, Efim Semenovich
Rockefeller University.
FA978
0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box.
1 box.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
A special collection of the Rockefeller University.
Former Classification: I 650 L846-U
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
Primarily contains biographical materials, correspondence and newspaper clippings.
- Biographical Materials, 1928, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- London, Raissa Eshman (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Photographs (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Article - Music from the Viewpoint of the Newest Ideas in Physics and Physiology (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1911-1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Reprints, 1920s (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Jewish Academy of Sciences, Certificate, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- National Academy of Sciences - Annual Meeting Schedule, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1903-1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)